Make me this time!
Looks like it all worked out.
Seems so.
Now it's time to choose your new crew member!
Who do you want, Straw Hat Luffy?
Come on, Chopper, get over here!
I'll miss you, Choppy!
I was so scared!
I'm so happy you won!
Are you kidding?
A bunch of suckers like that could never beat my crew.
We've seen blood, sweat, and plenty of tears today,
but the Davy Pack fight has finally drawn to a close.
With the Straw Hacks reclaiming their doctor, Tony Tony Chopper,
I say this match ends in a draw!
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Huh?
Any captain worth his way to Seaweed knows there are no draws in the pirate world.
It's plunder or be plunder.
You won't let it end like this, will you?
Wait, is he saying what I think he is?
Come on.
How about another three-coin game to decide which one of us is really the best?
Yeah, like we'd agree to that.
After all that cheating, you'd have to be an idiot to go for another round.
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no no no!
Oh no no no no no!
You're on, split head!
What if we were talking about?
We don't have anything to gain from this!
I don't want any of those losers that I proved!
So I think we'd be better off trading you to them!
Okay, this is the last time.
I won't do it again, I promise.
You're kidding.
I don't know if I have any tears left to cry.
He already agreed, so it's not like we can back out now.
I doubt he would go to the trouble if he didn't have something in mind.
Eh, I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Well, unless he's thinking he can nab us a shipwreck from Foxy's crew.
Screaming Hot Bombardment!
Pirate Dodgeball!
It's time for the second three-coin game!
The events this time are a team-wide dodgeball showdown,
a brutal new twist on a childhood favorite,
and a one-on-one boxing beatdown!
Like the previous game, each crew member can only participate twice!
In other words, last-minute light-up changes will not be allowed!
Oh, no two ways about it.
This time, they're gonna pick me for sure.
Yeah, right. I know they've got their eyes on me.
I'm doomed to spend the rest of my life as their poster girl.
Keep telling yourself that,
but we don't want either of you on our crew.
You're too scary, he's too weak.
With our second Daveyback fight of the day about to start,
I'm back in the announcer's seat to explain the rules of our first match.
The name of the game is Hit and Deadball!
The balls in question are the two you see on the field right now!
If the opposing team hits you with one of those babies,
you're out of the game!
The teams are divided into on-court and off-court members!
They're free to choose which ones go where and whatever number,
but once you run out of on-court members,
you lose the match!
Keep in mind that although the off-court members
can throw the ball around just like anyone else,
they are not allowed to enter the court under any circumstance!
They make it sound all fancy,
but it seems like regular old dodgeball to me.
There are some other miscellaneous details,
so be sure to read the rulebook carefully!
That's the rulebook?
You wouldn't expect it to be so thick.
Hit and Deadball is one of the greatest
and most time-honored Davey back-fight games!
Because it has been played so many times over the years,
more and more rules have been added to balance and perfect its form!
Only by strict adherence to these rules can the game truly be enjoyed!
What's the point in preaching to us about the rules
if you're going to break them all anyway?
Did you just give us the rulebook so we'll know how bad you're cheating?
No, no, no!
Take a look at the first page, mademoiselle!
Referee regulations.
He who makes a judgment contrary to the rules written here
shall be beheaded on the spot.
Beheaded? Scary!
And there you have it.
On that topic, this game will be officiated by a team of five referees
headed by a vet with 50 years of experience!
Roku Roshi!
With any luck, we might actually get a fair fight this time around.
Team Foxy has a veritable armada of players!
Truly a stupendous spectacle to see!
Sadly, the Straw Hats pale in comparison with their diminutive showing.
Sporting a measly seven members, I must wonder if they're even trying.
Okay, we get it!
Let's get this show on the road!
We'll start the match off with the double opening tip!
Each team bring two players to the center of the field!
Hey, do you mind if I do this?
Hmm?
Yeah, be my guest.
Go jump your heart out, little guy.
Oh, right!
Chopper has transformed!
It looks like he's not just Fluff after all!
He could turn out to be a powerful player for the Straw Hats!
Oh, no!
What's that?
Now he's not cute at all!
Ready, set, and go!
Nice catch!
Now give him a good spike to the face!
Aim straight for Splithead!
Come on, Chopper!
Let's go!
Wait!
Shit!
Oh, no!
Our boss is in trouble!
What?
He's already out of the game?
Yeah, you really showed their boss who's boss!
Safe!
What do you mean, safe?
That was a clean hit, you old fart!
It's a violation of Article 23!
Blows to the face do not count!
You're kidding!
Now what?
Well, boss, that looked like it hurt.
Don't laugh, Hamburg.
You're gonna make boss cry.
Get them while they're distracted!
Give them a good one for me, Sanji!
Yeah, I'll show them the power of our sweet love!
Here they come!
You might want to clear out of here!
Hey!
Take it easy!
We're still warming up here!
Hmph!
Eighteen members of Team Foxy are hereby eliminated for getting knocked out of bounds!
Way to go!
What a shock from the Straw Hats!
The Shep and the Swordsman both blew nine players right off the field!
Damn, I thought I'd get more than you.
Yeah, knock them dead, Sanji!
Knock them dead, Zoro!
Pardon me.
Wow, do you think we could take out nine people, too?
Nine?
I'll do ten!
Gum gum!
Slick shot!
Out of bounds!
Ten members from Team Foxy are eliminated!
Oh, yeah!
That's a new record!
Yet another strong showing from the Straw Hats!
They're thinning out the competition, but Team Foxy finally has them all!
Let's see how many I can knock out!
Go on, Chopper!
Even the score!
Nine, ten, eleven, or more!
Sure, you got it!
Ah!
The last-minute catch from Hamburg saves the day!
Now Team Foxy has both balls in their possession!
Could it finally be time for a comeback?
Poo-poo-poo!
Nice work as always, Hamburg!
Now why don't you pass those balls to Big Pan?
Roger, boss!
Right!
This is it!
Take them all out in one shot!
Poo-poo-poo!
boy!
Yeah, do they do you okay?
Good...
Not me!
Please, not me!
I do not, man!
What's up, no!
What happened? I can't see!
Out of bounds!
Mr. Longnose and 22 members of Team Foxy are hereby eliminated!
That looked bad. Are you okay?
Yeah, it takes more than that to kill me.
Hey, and look, I got the ball!
Big Pan's devastating dodgeball smash eliminated the Straw Hat's Longnose Sniper,
but caused a crushing amount of collateral damage to his own team.
Now Foxy and Hamburg are the only ones left on the field.
At this rate, the Foxy Pirates may be undone by their own strength.
The match is now 2-4!
What's next?
Who will reign supreme?
The Foxy Pirates
Hey, boss, what now?
What do you mean, what now?
I can't use my slow, slow beam as long as that archaeologist chick is here.
So there's only one choice left.
You mean you know what?
P-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p-p .
You know what, indeed.
Forum
What a turn of events!
Now Hamburg is out of the game, too!
Good one, Robin!
Hamburg is safe!
You sure? Article 54 states that while the face doesn't count,
the top of the head is still fair game.
If I were you, I'd start using my head first before somebody chops it off!
The girl is right! Hamburg is out!
I'm sorry, sir!
The Straw Hacks archaeologist has memorized the massive rulebook
in only moments by flexing the mighty muscles of her mind!
You read all that? Awesome!
Thanks for the compliment, but I'm only about halfway through.
Well, either way, they've only got one left, so let's finish them off quick!
You got it.
Hey, Sanji!
Yes, ladies?
Please don't hit our boss. Just give that ball to us, okay?
Of course!
You're so sweet!
Now would you mind getting knocked out of the game?
As a favor for me?
Why, it would be my pleasure, ma'am! You can hit me wherever you like!
If you don't get up, I'll knock you out!
Oh, love hunter Sanji has been blissfully bludgeoned and endearingly eliminated from the game!
Now he'll be joining his long-nosed companion on the sidelines!
Bye-bye!
You make me sick.
We should've seen that coming.
On the upside, their boss is the only one left.
We can't celebrate yet. You never know what might happen until the very end.
Yes, good point!
Huh? No way!
What the?
There it is! Hidden Deadpool's top secret weapon finally makes an appearance!
Say hello!
Who the Mr. Accu-cannon?
Hey, Raph, are you really gonna allow this? That thing is obviously against the rule!
So that's Mr. Accu-cannon?
Wait! Why are you acting like you know all about this doohickey? Did I miss something?
I ran across an article about it in the rule book, but I hadn't actually seen the device until now.
Rule number 322! The only weapon allowed is Mr. Accu-cannon!
Why would you make a rule just for that dumb thing?
I don't know! Seems pretty awesome to me!
What's the point? Listen, I don't care how big your Mr. Cannon whatever is, you're still gonna lose!
I wouldn't be so sure!
Hey, Porcha, you ready to finish him up?
I thought you'd never ask, boss! Better not blink. Flower hypnosis, go!
Not again!
Hurry up and close your eyes!
Oh!
Can you play without dirty tricks for once?
Now's your chance! Fire!
Oh, I will! Like shooting fish in a barrel!
I don't have to see, I can feel.
Even without my swords, I'm still a swordsman.
What power? The swordless swordsman not only sliced the ball in half with his bare hands, he did it with his eyes closed!
Oh no!
Zoro of Team Straw Hat is out!
Why, what'd I do?
Huh?
Rule number 645. Even with hands, no slicing the ball. Rules also state Foxy gets a new ball!
What?!
Oh well, battle on next time!
What a shame! It was an impressive move from Zoro, but the rules are the rules!
Are you okay? I don't think he's taking this too well.
Hey there, buddy!
Whatever you're about to say, I don't want to hear it, especially after that stunt you just pulled.
Whoa! The match is now 2 to 1! And Mr. Accu-Canon is ready to go!
Time to pick up where I left off!
Yeah? Then let's see what you've got!
Bring it on!
Ultra-fast level 5, go!
Let's see you dodge this, you brats!
No! Choppy!
The doctor makes a noble sacrifice for his captain, but is this the end for him?
Hey! They said hits to the face don't count, right?
Was that his face?
Huh! Now that you mention it, I'm not sure where that is exactly. With all that fluff, it's sorta hard to tell.
He's so brave!
Hey, ref, can't you see a pirates honor is at stake here? I'm telling you that was his face!
That's right! Any real man knows to show some respect when a pirate takes one for the team!
Hitting up face! Hitting up face! Hitting up face! Hitting up face! Hitting up face! Hitting up face! Hitting up face! Hitting up face! Hitting up face!
If pirates honor is at stake, then the choice is obvious, is it? The ball hit him in the face! And blows to the face do not count!
Blows to the face do not count!
You're the best!
However...
However?
Even if blows to the face don't count,
you're out of bounds, so you're still eliminated.
Say it ain't so!
This is a real tragedy!
Even after the Riff acknowledged his captain saving face block,
he's still out!
The brave little doctor will surely be missed by all!
Even so, he will be remembered as a true man of the sea!
Choppy!
Hey, you still hanging in there?
Yeah, but it doesn't matter.
I'm out of the game either way.
Don't worry. Leave the rest to me.
Oh, and thanks, Chopper. Nice save.
What makes you think I want to hear that?
That doesn't make me happy at all, you big jerk!
Not too bad, Choppy!
I can't wait till I win and you're back on my crew!
Gotta go through me first, Split-head!
Both teams are backed up against the wall
as our courageous captains face off in a climactic confrontation!
Heep, heep, heep, heep, heep!
I warn you, this is gonna hurt!
I think I'd give up now if I were you!
Huh! Why would I give up when you're the one who's gonna lose?
I wouldn't be so sure about that!
Why don't you take a good look around before you start spouting nonsense?
Here comes the Omnidirectional Sept!
Say your prayers, Butterboy!
What are they doing now?
Hey, what's up with those balls, old man?
That's gotta be against the rules!
The rulebook clearly states that players can use as many fake balls as they like!
You talk big, but you're just as bad as the last ref!
Damn, unless we can get a ref of our own, we're never gonna see the end of this!
Don't pay any attention to those guys, Luffy!
You and Foxy are the only ones with a real ball!
Just keep your eye on him!
Oh, how did she know?
What's wrong with this guy?
I'm starting to think his brain is split too!
They call me split brain, I swear I'm gonna cry!
Sorry, pal.
It looks like I'm gonna have to break your Mr. Whatchamacallit thing!
It's tiny!
There it goes!
Hello.
Hey, hey!
Yeah!
Hey!
Oh my!
Where'd this come from?
Better watch where you stretch that arm!
Come on, boys!
Let's shuffle!
Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! SHUFFLE TIME! SHUFFLE TIME! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time!
This is bad! If he can't tell which ones are real and which ones are fake he won't be able to dodge!
Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time! Shuffle Time!
Alright Mr. Smart Guy! Do you know which balls are real now?
Better figure it out fast, before they hit you!
Shut up! I'll just catch all the balls and then it won't matter!
Don't you get snarky with me, boy!
Just sit back and accept your defeat with grace.
Now, time to let those balls fly!
Heh, nice try. But you're finished.
Hey, look out behind you!
Luffy, don't dodge! Let it hit your face!
Right, easy for you to say.
He did it!
All right!
Oh!
Straw hat, Luffy! You're out!
Why? I thought it didn't count if you got hit in the face!
Rule 999.
Interesting any part of the ball results in instant disqualification.
Check the rulebook yourself if you don't believe me.
Unfortunately, he's correct. It's on the very last page.
What?
Why does that rule even exist?
It's over!
Straw hat, Luffy has hit his way to defeat as Team Foxy claims victory in the first round!
Not again!
...
Warpiece! Showdown on the cliff! Red light, green light!
Huh? Did Zoro get lost again?